http://www.fjsb.com/privacy-statement.html

Member FDIC
Rates subject to change.
Substantial interest penalty for early withdrawal.
Rates effective as of the date of this issue.
Fees could reduce earnings.
The Fort Jennings State Bank Privacy Statement
Visitors to the on-line home of The Fort Jennings State Bank remain anonymous. We do not collect identifying information about visitors who access our World Wide Web home page.
Our host uses standard software to collect non-identifying information, such as:
Date and time our site was accessed.
IP address (a numeric address given to computers connected to the Internet).
Pages in web site which were viewed.
Country of visitor.
The Fort Jennings State Bank does not use this information to create statistics of usage or interest in our site. This information is not disseminated or sold to any other organizations.
WE WANT YOU TO BE ASSURED THAT WE WILL NOT OBTAIN PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION ABOUT YOU WHEN YOU VISIT OUR SITE, UNLESS YOU CHOOSE TO PROVIDE SUCH INFORMATION TO US VOLUNTARILY.
The Internet banking site of The Fort Jennings State Bank is a secured area. You will need a username and password in order to access the site. Please do not share this information. It is the policy of the Bank to maintain appropriate security standards and procedures regarding unauthorized access to customer information. In those instances where personal information is needed to process a customer request, such as a loan application submitted via electronic mail, the information is used internally, only as appropriate, to handle the customer’s request. This information is not disseminated or sold to any other organizations.
The Fort Jennings State Bank has always maintained a high standard of confidentiality, which we feel is an indispensable part of our reputation for honesty and integrity. This Privacy Statement is intended to insure that all visitors understand that The Fort Jennings State Bank will only collect, retain and use that information of our customers which the Bank reasonably believes is useful (and allowed by law) to administer the customers financial business with the Bank and to provide products, services and other opportunities to our customers.
Privacy Disclosure Document Form
If you would like to view our full privacy statement, click the link below.
You may also use this form to opt-out of sharing your personal information with nonaffiliates.
Privacy StatementThis opens a PDF document.
Fort Jennings 120 North Water St. • Fort Jennings, Ohio 45844
PH: 419-286-2527 • Fax: 419-286-2409
Lobby Hours:
• Monday-Wednesday 9:00 am - 3:00 pm
• Thursday 9:00 am - 11:00 am
• Friday 9:00 am - 5:30 pm
• Saturday 9:00 am - 11:30 am
Drive Thru Hours: Drive-Thru window opens at 8:30 A.M. each day and is open until the closing time listed for each day above, except Thursday until 12:00 pm.
Ottoville 120 East Main St. • Ottoville, Ohio 45876
PH: 419-453-2527 • Fax: 419-453-2409
Lobby Hours:
• Monday-Wednesday 9:00 am - 3:00 pm
• Thursday 9:00 am - 12:00 pm
• Friday 9:00 am - 5:30 pm
• Saturday 9:00 am - 11:30 am
Drive Thru Hours: Drive-Thru window opens at 8:30 A.M. each day and is open until the closing time listed for each day above.
Columbus Grove 302 Delphos Road • Columbus Grove, Ohio 45830
PH: 419-659-2527 • Fax: 419-659-2509
Lobby Hours:
• Monday-Wednesday 9:00 am - 4:00 pm
• Thursday 9:00 am - 12:00 pm
• Friday 9:00 am - 5:00 pm
• Saturday 9:00 am - 11:30 am
Drive Thru Hours: Drive-Thru window opens at 8:30 A.M. each day and is open until the closing time listed for each day above.
Leipsic 12 East Main Street • Leipsic, Ohio 45856
PH: 419-943-2528 • Fax: 419-943-2809
Lobby Hours:
• Monday-Wednesday 9:00 am - 4:00 pm
• Thursday 9:00 am - 12:00 pm
• Friday 9:00 am - 5:00 pm
• Saturday 9:00 am - 11:30 am
Drive Thru Hours: Drive-Thru window opens at 8:30 A.M. each day and is open until the closing time listed for each day above.
Ottawa 1300 N Locust Street • Ottawa, Ohio 45875
PH: 419-523-3013 • Fax: 419-523-3281
Lobby Hours:
• Monday, Tuesday & Thursday 9:00 am - 4:00 pm
• Wednesday 9:00 am - 12:00 pm
• Friday 9:00 am - 5:00 pm
• Saturday 9:00 am - 11:30 am
Drive Thru Hours: Drive-Thru window opens at 8:30 A.M. each day and is open until the closing time listed for each day above, except Thursday until 5:00 pm
Continental 100 S Main Street • Continental, Ohio 45831
PH: 419-596-2527 • Fax: 419-596-3257
Lobby Hours:
• Monday, Tuesday & Thursday 9:00 am - 4:00 pm
• Wednesday 9:00 am - 12:00 pm
• Friday 9:00 am - 5:00 pm
• Saturday 9:00 am - 11:30 am
Drive Thru Hours: Drive-Thru window opens at 8:30 A.M. each day and is open until the closing time listed for each day above, except Thursday until 5:00 pm
Close
Our Purpose
Our purpose is to become "the Bank of choice" in the communities we serve.
We will accomplish this by offering to our customers the financial services they expect while providing a return to our owners. In accomplishing this mission, we will remain an independent community bank.
With six convenient locations, 24 hour ATM's, on-line banking and a friendly, well trained staff, you won't go wrong making The Fort Jennings State Bank your bank of choice. Whether you're looking for the best way to protect your cash assets, loans to meet your personal, business, agricultural or real estate needs, or just looking for friendly experienced staff, The Fort Jennings State Bank is your choice.
Contact Us
If you would like to contact us, please call:
419-286-2527
Or click below to use our online contact forms.
